[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the male lead in Rabbit Test?", "correct_answer": "Billy Crystal", "incorrect_answers": ["Alex Porter", "Gary Shandling", "Johnny  Rocco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How fast have winds on Jupiter blown?", "correct_answer": "430 Kilometers per hour(267 Miles per hour)", "incorrect_answers": ["240 Kilometers per hour(150 Miles per hour)", "470 Kilometers per hour(292 Miles per hour)", "360 Kilometers per hour(223 Miles per hour)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do Napoleon and Trisha get to the school dance in the comedy movie Napoleon Dynamite?", "correct_answer": "Pedros cousins drive them in their low-rider.", "incorrect_answers": ["They walk the whole 5 miles.", "They rent a limo.", "Trishas mom take them there in their van."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the range of the pH scale?", "correct_answer": "(0 or 1) -- 14", "incorrect_answers": ["14 -- 20", "0 -- 7", "-7 -- 0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which language does the word  algebra derive?", "correct_answer": "Arabic", "incorrect_answers": ["Greek", "Latin", "Sanskrit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress won the Academy Awards for Best Actress for the 1960 movie BUtterfield 8?", "correct_answer": "Elizabeth Taylor", "incorrect_answers": ["Bette Davis", "Greta Garbo", "Audrey Hepburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who made the following statement: We were both trained for this. When in doubt... kill.?", "correct_answer": "Richard Crenna in First Blood", "incorrect_answers": ["Val Kilmer in Top Gun", "Sylvester Stallone in Rambo II", "Tom Berenger in Sniper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these conditions is the most common reason for a doctor to prescribe Lithium?", "correct_answer": "Bipolar disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Anemia", "Diabetes", "Glaucoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Mario video game series, Marios arch enemy, Bowser, uses what reptilian creatures as his chief henchmen?", "correct_answer": "Koopatroopas", "incorrect_answers": ["Snakes", "Goombas", "Raptors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you multiplied all the whole numbers together, what would the answer be ?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["aleph zero", "infinite", "infinity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word can mean: 1) the upper part of a shoe that covers the instep; 2) an improvised accompaniment in music; 3) a seductive woman.", "correct_answer": "vamp", "incorrect_answers": ["tramp", "truel", "hypoxiol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Aliens, who were the tough hombres that accompanied Ripley back to LV-426?", "correct_answer": "Colonial Marines", "incorrect_answers": ["Space Marines", "F Troop", "Rescue Rangers"]}]